# **Ayush Dangol**

# **UI/UX Engineer**

Bramatole, Teku Kathmandu 9840098522 ayushdangol215@gmail.com

# **PROJECTS**

# **Project Name** — Quick caller

Worked with the team to develop an android app called Quick caller. The app is for educational institutes where in case of emergency regarding students, the teachers or any other responsible personnel can quickly get details such as guardian number, address, blood group etc.

#### Role:

- Helped with the design of the application.
- Helped with the front-end Development of the application.

## **Technology Used:**

- Adobe XD
- Android Studio

# **Project Name** — *Travel Buddy*

As part of a college project I developed an android application that recommends a user a travel plan using a recommendation engine.

## Role:

 Designed, Developed and implemented by myself as it was an individual project.

## **Technology Used:**

- Adobe XD
- Android Studio
- Firebase

# **Project Name** — Personal Web Portfolio

My own web portfolio which I designed and developed.

# **Technology Used:**

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- Github

# **SKILLS**

#### **Technical Skills:**

UI Design, React js, Vue js, Node js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, Javascript, Vs code and Git.

Familiar with design and prototyping tools such as Figma, Adobe XD and Adobe photoshop.

#### **Soft Skills:**

**Teamwork and Communication** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Vianet Communications, Jawalakhel**- *Jr. Tech Support Executive* september 2019 – september 2020

Handle technical issues related to the Internet for Home based Clients.

**Shree Bhakta Vidyashram, Chhetrapati** - *Computer Science Instructor* August 2017 - April 2019

• Provide knowledge about computer science and it's technologies to students of class 6, 7, 8.

# Nepa Pucha Foundation, Kuleshwor - Field Worker

August 2017 - May 2019

- Come up with ideas for meetups and events for field works.
- Handle all the planning and scheduling for field work.
- Circulate information to all team members effectively.
- Make sure all things went as planned at the field work
- Retrospect the field visit with the team members.

# **EDUCATION**

**Herald College, Hadigaun** - Bachelor's degree in Information Technology

November 2017 - July 2020

# **EXTRA**

Ex-Co-leader and Co-Founder of the Herald College's Herald Devcorps UI & Visuals Community.